all right I was talking in my own
personal my own personal self and
realized I realize I felt I should be
getting here because there's a
possibility here there's no possibility
better
that means possibility excites for me
it pulls me forward and of course I was
saying amazing things there we're not
were do is going to be hearing you know
here I'll just look like a fool that's
cool I'm done with that that's part of
the whole whole process is being okay
with how it unfolds and I have my next
point time I universal you know universe
the universe giving me GPS coordinates I
have the next thing tomorrow and I'm
nervous and excited about that just
sitting here as always trying to explain
this process and allowing the process
and Myra it's wonderful the issue is a
lot of it's done I didn't see purchased
in secret okay how do you publicize your
internal thoughts right sometimes I
write them down on paper a lot of times
are good on paper way too much paper
it's trees but having yeah then it goes
on internally so city that are talking
to myself okay here goes just slightly
the rancor subtracting two people it
could potentially be watching and the
career daddy it's not me doing that and
to just be talking to myself I would
have written here whether anyone else
wants it a cartoon wardrobe that's just
one one outfit you wear Audrey he all
the time different items aren't wearing
the same thing always but like 20 blue
shirts and shorts maybe like tights and
a t-shirt I'm sure it's what's
comfortable but one outfit forever
oh yeah mind can be like a dragon onesie
so like profound thought
need to get out in the world it's gonna
say that somebody's like that's not oh
we can have a world of peace of
prosperity for everyone
he's a prosperity we just need to create
it together we have enough
we have enough ingenuity we have enough
people who care deeply one mean 1
million people wanted to create change
each paid $10 Candide into for 10
million we design systems and tech to
help everyone who uses them like their
lives loving our limitations yeah see
that's clear everyone know we're doing
that perfect that's great but this whole
process it's the whole point of it is
that it's ridiculous we require people
to have a certain skill set that's not
actually related to being better at the
task if my ability to communicate this
idea in no way actually reflects my
ability to come up with this idea
it definitely hinders it but it doesn't
make it any less of an of a solution it
just makes it more frustrating but it's
like you don't understand it so that you
can see this well let me I can explain
it like global cooperative cuz that's
awesome so then we created together with
democracy and transparency the world
when we get to the people who have
access to the knowledge of our
politicians and the corporations we
support and the products that they sell
us so we don't have to rely on branding
and we don't have to rely on the biased
media whatever that is whatever it means
to you where you can see the actual
facts we then require like politicians
act ethically in radical yes of course
but also no having our politicians are
having corporations designed for the
piece they think isn't capitalism in
markets and isn't that like the consumer
has infinite knowledge so we'll support
only things that are going to be in our
best interest well no we're not we're
destroying the planet
living the labor lives we don't have the
whole picture of information we don't
know what a chocolate bar truly costs to
other humans to the planet and so the
more we can see that I mean therefore
make it more efficient together and make
it better together the better I think
that communism failed in the past
because we really suck at something
planning and we also suck at giving over
Authority and having these inner circles
of knowing versus not and the idea was
it was never supposed to stay that way
and of course people don't hand over
power so you don't have that ever you
create with open transparency and the
hoc solutions in this inefficiency of
competition where you create an industry
and there's garbage created and then
these inputs that are needed and you're
having all these ripple effects on the
environment and other people's worlds
and that train of thought is calm that's
helpful why hold on to trains but his
speeding through like someone someone
who's not gonna watch this or get
something about that peace like we just
need to connect the right people
together that's it
oh yeah that's all we have to do and I
think we can absolutely do that
create a system where we can trust each
other because we've designed it to trust
each other
so that like well if I'm meeting you for
the first time what gives me trust
online well if I know you know a friend
of mine that's gonna help if I can talk
to my friend and get them to say how
they know you and that gives a definite
level of trust then I know you're one
person and not a corporation or a bot
like that you're an actual human being
representing your own interests right
like there's certain things we want to
know well if I want to know that people
probably won't know that about me like
what are we willing to share what we
really do a request and and what does
that look like together is it growth
right where can you develop that level
of trust not hierarchy doubt like it
everyone asked
I have the retina scan it's like no how
do we know to trust people if we're
selling them things that we're gonna get
it back maybe that's one reading system
because people aren't one individual
right like maybe they really suck in
finances and you want to be able to get
the money before like I think
that's generally how it works can I send
the goods but figuring out I guess
person always return two things as
person always like just the fertility
and maybe there's like we figure that
out together say I think those people
know I don't know what they're I return
things more or less than other people I
don't have that shame in returning
things like this doesn't work it's
crappy I paid money on it it needs to be
returned that take advantage of like
corporations return policies like
Costco's which is amazing it's also why
I shop there ever random thoughts that
like I have a vision and a somewhat
knowledge that Costco is it is a much
better company than Walmart but it's
just somewhat Brandi somewhat facts of
like how much they pay their employees
what they the benefits their employees
have the requirements they have and how
they treat their employees like there's
better basics but I don't fully know
that cuz I don't have that published
somewhere like what do people start at
and what do people make what do people
cuz we can as people who work for those
companies make sure that information
like here's what I make for our and
here's where here's my demographics look
they pay me less because I'm female
because whatever it happens to be right
we can share that information if we want
to again we're not necessarily sharing
here's my here's my paycheck right I can
understand I don't feel feels
comfortable with that nobody but we're
sharing our own data so it's okay I'm
willing to share that money employer X
hates me this amount and I can't even
take a picture of it if we're still
getting physical checks and have my name
blurred out or not you can actually see
and track it but where it goes up it's
blacked out right or it's like people
can see that it is whatever
seems to be not there for security
reasons are not there and yeah pretty
good having that information washed and
safe for people to use right so we can
see a corporation's paid all these
people and demographics we have the
picture of the check to prove it that
this person is is it or assuming and
they're not we're not I'm not able to
just log on to the site and be one
person at one time and be like yes I am
a 17 year old boy with blue hair right
like it's like no or not I have to be me
because the information is washed so
it's all connected together in the
backend so we don't have to so we can
have that level of trust and have
reliable data when it's offered up
freely and safely so that have we got
the best of all worlds I'm getting
nervous how you put something on but
yeah that's piece of it it's like I use
like parts I'm I'm like okay you got me
share this these burns
might sound but like everything is
coming down the pipeline we want
corporations to do it or do we want to
do it do we want to make it so that we
can decide what is ethically okay okay
for us to do on the internet rescue
within our organisation yeah nothing
like get inside me sidetrack enjoy 10
times you can if there's enough people
out there currently who have solutions
to our current problems they just have
all their own personal limitations
they're stressed out you don't know how
to get it out in the world because
they're working two jobs and have you
know a parent or a child who's sick like
we need to help take care of one another
so that we can release that and it
doesn't we don't fix everything at once
but with enough of us working on things
that are meaningful to us how do you fix
everything wrong Laurens like not the
beginning in the beginning we need to
concentrate our energies so that there
is more
but there's one project that's thriving
it's because I needs to be enough money
and human ingenuity and manpower and
whatever not engendered word that is
that we create a world that makes sense
together and the beauty is that the
world were currently in is destroying us
it's on a trajectory down the path
banging into a freaking wall but we also
have some time and we can allow it to do
what it's doing at the level it's doing
it at well we fix everything around it
like we are we have there's food in the
market everywhere but like in my markets
there's food there's hospitals running
they're just perfect no and we let
people where you're called to do stuff
where you're fighting for your minimum
wage we're fighting for universal health
care how can people do that creating the
tools to help people collaborate in that
area but also not that's the only focus
because it's like we can actually create
our own systems from within that help us
live healthier get free education
I mean we're fighting for universal
education and universities it looks like
this is how they should exist and I
should get to go away and go to call
attention like the why why is that how
we if I'm an employee player and I'm
hiring someone what level of education
do I want them to have what level of
education do I want to have to be able
to do that job
between those two it's like this is what
we need we don't need a four-year degree
to do it's like no we want someone to
fulfill these types of tasks here's how
we train them for that who wants to do
it like it's it's not like free edge but
free education would be very different
right there's online units to learn
absolutely anything those cohorts you
can do it with if you learn better and
improve theirs we don't need to recreate
the current system we can create
something that's much more efficient and
meets our needs because we can both say
what our needs are and change our needs
right we could be like oh as employer
I care you're gonna do the job I care
that like the people get along and are
cohesive I care that everyone makes a
decent living and a relatively
stress-free so they can give their best
the selves holder here in whatever time
period that looks like and we can
support them in the best way
I remember when I'm talking about I have
like this beard or injustice he's just
talking to myself for 20 minutes I'm in
no way gonna bark at these or advertise
it you know she's gonna need to
algorithm and everything existence or
something
- if this is part of it right at the
downtime or you're not already thinking
about anything or you are not fertilizer
that's also a piece of it
we spend so much of our human time doing
mundane and I don't mean like
talking on Facebook and watching
television and things that like we enjoy
but society says you should probably see
about I mean actually wasting our time
like going to jobs that don't mean
anything that don't actually help anyone
or create anything you don't help our
soul get better don't like they just
they're only there to make certain
people mature they're only there to
propagate a system that's broken like
it's like okay that's not super
meaningful and I think we all feel that
it's like a job and we like rank them
based on salary instead of like anything
like contribution or how happy they make
us or how amazing our co-workers are
it's like don't you want to work with
people that you enjoy working with in a
way that works for your life and
projects that are meaningful where
you're able to get the skills you need
to do those things they call to you
where the ways that you aren't adequate
or venture up in society are helped by
technology if you're required to improve
like that you're required to show up on
time there's technology to help people
who don't show up on time if you're
required to have a certain level of
social etiquette but those rules are
spelled out for people who need those
are all spelled out and not this
requirement like that we are more
different in the morals we have
different intelligences and different
needs and do we create a world that
works for everyone just by honoring that
like it doesn't mean that everything
needs to work for everyone
it's like know what works for someone
who's single sided deaf probably works
for other people on versing design of
dev and so when I create solutions for
myself I can share them with other
people and vice versa
and when someone creates something who
happens to have a child like that or is
like that they can offer it to the world
if what they want to do is solely make a
profit on it
but the system exists go out there do
that but what if they want is to get it
out in the world and offer their thought
ingenuity to the world and possibly make
some money at it possibly there's a way
where you Pony pull the lid off of what
they contribute when it's if it went
it's big innit
and we all agree on that but it's mainly
done because it's a solution and you
want it out in the real world and that's
like yeah you can keep a piece of it
it's like you created it and you're just
oh so the whole process is like whatever
kernel you start out you still need the
rest of the process happen with everyone
else but I'm not we can decide together
that people can use it for business and
our own energy business and what that
what that mean so there's a fee you pay
whether it's a membership to whether
businesses you have to give us 10% your
prison is like whether you all many
businesses that we own at least 10% of
Chim these our products in our community
connection and you gotta me up that to
like sorry you need to be 1% cuz it's
not we like the people who work those
businesses the people who almost misses
this can also be members and vote but
everyone else gets to vote to so if it's
in everyone else's best interests that
you not be part of it because we don't
own 51% and you're working your own
self-interest or not the self-interest
to everyone else you want the 1% so we
can have ownership and that's what we
vote as that we get it up to that point
or really know when you think you
understand you have ownership things
they're gonna use our products like
we're the ones who did that right they
can you hear the ones who created it
together so it's not coming from the top
down like we are the ones who almost
businesses and work at them we're like
no we want the ones that are
contributing to everybody that we all
have a say in an all democratic and
transparent because that's our values
and that's what we're based on let's
change it one more minute
I did this Pacific time if there be more
people on also I'm not doing is this
Pacific done like there is an actually
right people to see this system people
who are subscribed do they like is it no
how do you have to be logged on during
this time very the next one comes after
that it's like that's the next thing
you're supposed to do that
why haven't you done that is that time
yet universe it's like hotels bastard
four months later you've done the thing
that could have taken a week ridiculous
supers oh and I mean now so let's take
it off so why